One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Once there was a man who obtained everything, the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His last words before he was executed inspired people to sail the seas.
All my wealth and treasure?
It can be yours if you want!
Search for it!
I left everything in that one place.
People now set sail in search of romance.
The world has entered a Great Age of Pirates!
I can't stay still! I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn.
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep.
If we're going to go to an incredible world,
you'll have to be tough.
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner ( • v • )
Freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow.
I'm sure we'll be the first to find One Piece!
Our hearts dream beyond measure...
so let's never wake them up.
I can't stay still! I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... made it this far.
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us,
and we won't leave anyone behind.
We'll go at it with all our hearts, that's a vow.
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still! I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
The Mermaid Princess in Hard-Shell Tower!
Shirahoshi of the Neptune Family!
Member of the Flying Pirates
Great Monk Wadatsumi (Giant Puffer Fishman)
Wadatsumi.
No response yet?
Has Princess Shirahoshi still not sent a letter back?
Nah, not yet, Captain Decken.
Ah, how many years have I been waiting now?
About ten, right? She's probably not gonna answer...
In short, this is all that despicable Neptune's fault!
He wants to force her into a political marriage...
I presume!
The fact that he's been keeping her locked inside that steel tower for 10 years proves it!
Oh, how tragic!
Despite the fact that she and I are in love...
I presume!
Bullhead Shark Fishman
Captain of the Flying Pirates
Vander Decken IX
Princess Shirahoshi!
No matter how long I wander the ocean floor, I'll never find another woman as great or as beautiful as you!
If our love is mutual, then all is well.
However, I can not allow you to live with another man.
If you do, then you must die, Shirahoshi!
It's either "Death or Marriage" for you!
Today, I will once again send you an axe with the emblem of a single rose on it.
Accept it, Shirahoshi!
It is the symbol of our marriage!
Captain... You completely missed the target.
You imbecile! I never miss my target...
I presume!
It came back!
It's flying toward Ryuuguu Palace!
Ryuuguu Kingdom Royal Palace
Ryuuguu Palace
H-Hey! What's wrong?!
I'm just a pirate who came here to get some food!
Come on!
Hey!
Oh, shut up... What a pain.
Princess Shirahoshi is crying!
It's coming from Hard-Shell Tower!
What happened to the tower's guards!?
What?! Why is nobody with her?!
We're sorry, Sir! There was a mix-up with the shifts.
A human has come to take my life,
and has made it inside my room!
Huh? No!
Hey, that's not it!
I was just hungry, and didn't know this was your food!
An axe? Where'd it come from?
Are you alright?
You're not hurt anywhere, are you?!
You were screaming louder than usual,
so we were worried.
What are you doin-
Is there an intruder in here?!
I-I'm sorry to have made you worry. I must have had a nightmare.
I could have sworn I heard a voice.
Well...
Oh, and speaking of which,
there is something I must tell you.
It's about the pirate Straw Hat Luffy,
who apparently rescued Megalo earlier.
Some mermaids have gone missing,
and we suspect he has kidnapped them.
Also, due to a prediction by Madame Shyarly, we've decided to confine the Straw Hats to the dungeon,
as there is a good chance that they will cause trouble in the future.
The swordsman who came
to Ryuuguu Palace a little while ago...
fell asleep after drinking too much,
and we have already placed him under arrest.
The three members of Straw Hat's crew who arrived just now have probably been captured too.
However, their captain, Straw Hat, who came here with them must have realized what was going on...
and somehow, he's disappeared.
We believe he may be lurking
somewhere in the castle, so please be careful.
We will also make sure we capture
the rest of his crewmates on the island.
We will protect the country's peace at all costs!
Well, in any case, it's really quite a shame that we had to restrain Megalo's saviors.
Oh, right... It has already been five minutes.
We will be leaving now.
Thank you so much.
I really was quite rude to you earlier.
Please, forgive me.
I didn't know you were the one who saved Megalo's life.
May I call you Luffy-sama?
Sure.
Luffy-sama, since you are a pirate...
does that mean you are a bad person?
I don't know. Decide that for yourself.
B-But what about your crewmates?
They've been captured by our guards.
Oh, it's alright. There's no way you guys could actually capture them.
Is that so?
Well, never mind that. What was with that axe?
What kind of superman could have thrown that, and from where?
I know... who did it.
It's a man named Vander Decken-sama.
He did it to get revenge, since I refused to marry him.
That man...
The devil placed the curse of "Target" on him.
Because of this, he's capable of...
targeting my life from anywhere at any time,
since he has set me as his target.
That's why it's dangerous for me to go outside.
I'm not even allowed to take a single step outside Hard-Shell Tower.
He has been doing it for ten years.
Ten years?!
Must be really boring.
And on top of that, my father has decided that the guards can only be in here...
for five minutes at a time.
Really?
And so, Megalo is the only one I can talk to.
He's a valuable friend of mine.
So that's why they wanted
to hold a feast just for saving him.
That kinda got ruined, though.
Regardless of that, you humans certainly do eat a lot for your size.
The shaggy old guy...
said we'd have a feast...
but he just kept getting yelled at for so long.
I couldn't wait any longer...
so I came here, following the smell.
By the way, they called you "Princess", right?
Yes.
So you're the Mermaid Princess?
Yes. I am the daughter of King Neptune.
My name is Shirahoshi.
Huh? Shirasu?
No, Shirahoshi.
Huh... That's really hard to say.
Ah! I want to taste that too!
You don't seem like a bad person to me at all.
Since you are a pirate,
have you gone on adventures and such?
Yeah!
Oh, right. And have you seen the sun?
When night falls, one can see stars floating in the sky, right?
And there are many different kinds of flowers, and animals with fur all over their bodies!
Have you ever been to a green place called the "forest"?
Wait, wait!
You're asking too many questions! Wait a second!
Alright.
My, what large cheeks you have.
What are you doing?! Stop that!
O-O-Oh no...
Please don't yell at me so loudly.
Luffy-sama... You really are scary... after all.
Hey! Why are you crying? Cut it out!
Nobody has ever... scolded me before.
Even though you're so huge,
you're just a weakling and a crybaby, aren't you?
I don't like you!
What an awful thing to say.
Nobody has ever said such a thing to me.
You are just awful... Please leave.
I...
I can't take this anymore!
I'm stuffed!
Thanks for the food!
You've been in here for ten years, huh? I'd probably get ill from that.
Luffy-sama... Please leave now.
Say...
Is there anywhere you wanna go?
Of course... There are many places.
I'd bet there are.
Then let's get out of here!
What?!
Let's go for a walk!
No wait! I can't do that.
What's with you? Let's go!
It'll be alright!
If anything else comes flying at you,
I'll just blow it all away!
What?!
Usopp-chin! Nami-chin! Brook-chin!
Ryuuguu Palace
Main Entrance
Can't you even restrain them?!
They're just three humans!
Hey, what are you doing?!
Everyone, if you keep fighting them,
you really will be considered criminals!
Be that as it may, we don't have a good reason to just quietly accept this either, Caimie-san.
I was really looking forward to the feast at Ryuuguu Palace, too.
If we don't fight back, we'll be captured.
They were the ones who turned against us for some incomprehensible reason!
I can take on as many of you as you like, if you so desire.
They're this strong, even without their captain!
T-They're too powerful!
Whatever we may or may not do in the future...
Do you honestly think
we'll let you arrest us for it now?!
Was the guy with the nose always this reliable?!
See?! This is just the prologue to the future that was foretold!
Look who's talking!
If you hadn't attacked us,
we'd have no reason to fight you!
Though, these guys aren't anywhere near as tough as the giant insects on the Boin Islands!
Behold the power of my new weapon,
the Black Kabuto!
Come at me from wherever you want!
Neptune-sama, please help us!
Is it really alright to arrest someone due to a prophecy?
I would like some time to think about it -jamon!
Therefore I would like you to allow yourselves to be captured for the time being!
He is quite a formidable foe!
Zoro?!
I thought you were in a prison cell?!
I heard the festival music...
so I came here!
Wait right there, Wadatsumi.
Fishman District, "Noah"
Right, understood.
Vander Decken-sama has arrived!
Right this way.
Pardon the delay.
I ran into a volcanic eruption on the way.
Are you the owner of this place? The infamous Hody,
I presume?
Just as infamous as you are.
The crazy Vander Decken.
Glad to be working with you.
Oh, a handshake?
That's a problem. Wait a second.
This'll do.
Oh, don't worry about it!
The pleasure's all mine.
Nice to meet ya, Hody Jones.
Now, nobody on the ocean floor can oppose us.
All the dangerous guys are gathered here!
Decken! Decken!
Hody! Hody!
Neptune is a nuisance for both of us.
We both share the same objectives.
To crush the Neptune Army, who have neither the pride of fishmen nor merfolk.
To take the head of Sea God Neptune.
And...
to bring Ryuuguu Kingdom...
to ruin!
What have you guys done?!
Really,
you went way too far!
Indeed! Apologize for your actions!
You were the ones who started this fight! We're all in this together, you idiots!
We just wanted to threaten them and run away!
And I just wanted to go sightseeing and shopping.
Well, it's in the past now, so what can we do?
Don't complain!
"What can we do"?! You think that's good enough?!
Just dropping by Fishman Island and then casually occupying Ryuuguu Palace...
How ruthless can you get?!
Ow...
So should we just have let them arrest us?!
I keep telling you, we should have just threatened them and fled!
First off, we don't know how we could escape. Second, Luffy's not here!
Yeah, that's right, Luffy's gone!
Where did he go?
Where indeed?
We're really in a hurry here.
So don't be mean, and just tell us.
Yeah, we need to find Luffy!
Where is the treasure chamber?
Cut it out!
What? Why?
Why are you acting all innocent?! Consider our situation!
Now, everyone!
In this difficult time, let's sing a song and be happy!
Come on!
It'll work out somehow, it'll work out somehow.
And even if it doesn't, we'll die someday anyway!
Yeah!
You shut up too, Soul King!
Neptune-sama, are you alright?!
I can't believe that the champion of the sea, King Neptune, would end up like this.
My bad hip acted up
all of a sudden, so I couldn't fight.
I've really gotten old.
Quite a blunder -jamon!
Sorry!
We should have moved quickly and burst their bubble,
turning it into an underwater fight,
but they managed to get rid of all the water instead!
Listen up, you scum!
Once the three brothers of the Neptune Army, Prince Fukaboshi, Prince Ryuuboshi,
and Prince Manboshi get back here,
you're going to regret this!
In any case, we can't stay on Fishman Island any longer.
Where is the Sunny?
We need to gather everyone up and set sail.
But the Sunny's coating was torn off
as we entered the island.
The Log Pose has been acting strange too.
Ever since we came here,
it hasn't shown any sign of stabilizing.
You're hopeless. You can't navigate
the New World with such a simple Pose.
You ignorant pirates.
Huh? This won't work?
What do you mean?
I'll tell you if you untie me.
That must be Prince Fukaboshi!
Akkamanbo! Yay! Yay!
Hmm? How peculiar.
What could the guards be doing?
Hello, who is this?
Hey! Why are you answering?!
Prince Fukaboshi!
Help us!
Be quiet, you two!
Prince Ryuuboshi!
Prince Manboshi!
Oh my! Brother, something
must have happened -la-ti-do!
I think so too! Are Father and Shirahoshi alright?!
It's me, Fukaboshi. What is going on in there?
Lower the connecting channel right now, and let us in.
And what will happen if we do that?
No can do!
H-Hey! What are you saying?!
Explain the situation to them!
That's right! In that case, tie me and Caimie up too!
We don't want to be seen as your partners in crime!
Zoro-chin, you're scaring me!
Are you, by any chance, one of Straw Hat's companions?
Fukaboshi! He's the swordsman with the three swords from the Straw Hat Crew...
Pirate Hunter Zori!
It's Zoro!
Father?!
You hear that? We've got plenty of hostages, including Neptune!
If you want them to live,
then start making preparations for us to set sail!
What we'll need is our ship, the Sunny, re-coated.
We don't know where it is, so you guys find it.
Also, the rest of our crew.
One gloomy woman. One robot.
One raccoon dog, and one pervy water imp.
Oh, Zoro! 1,000,000,000 belly, too.
Cut it out, damn it!
A pervy water imp! How fitting!
That fits him perfectly!
This is no time to be laughing!
Pervy water imp!
Come on! At least make a jab at the "gloomy woman" comment too!
I understand your conditions.
I will make arrangements for you and your crew
to leave this kingdom safely.
However, you must return all of the hostages unharmed!
Brother!
We have no other choice.
The connecting channel is the only way
into Ryuuguu Palace.
Everywhere else, it's protected by a thick bubble layer
that we can't break through.
May I say one more thing, Zoro-kun?
I'd rather not tell you in this situation,
but I cannot dishonor my debt to Jinbe.
From the former Royal Warlord of the Sea, Sea Knight Jinbe, to Straw Hat Luffy.
He wanted me to tell you this once you reached the island.
I have two messages to pass on.
Jinbe, huh?
Jinbe?!
Boss Jinbe.
Oh yeah, he did say that he was friends with Jinbe.
Despite being a pirate, he's an amazing man who everyone on the island trusts.
Luffy isn't here right now, but I'll pass the message on to him.
Say it.
The first message is...
"Don't fight Hody."
The second one is...
"I will be waiting for you in the Sea Forest."
That is all.
The Sea Forest... Hody...
Fishman Island
Coral Hill
They really did it!
Apparently the Straw Hat Pirates have occupied Ryuuguu Palace!
What?!
What's their objective?!
No way! And they seemed like such nice people.
How could they?
Kidnapping the girls from the bay,
and considering the future that was predicted...
It has to be them!
Things are progressing in that direction!
They've finally shown their true colors!
Apparently two of Straw Hat's companions are in the back room of the Mermaid Café.
The guards just went to capture them.
Kung Fu Point!
Sanji is still recovering! Don't touch him!
What do you mean "come to Ryuuguu Palace"?! You're just planning to arrest us, aren't you?!
Hey... you guys...
Sanji! You mustn't move around yet!
So, will she be at that Ryuuguu Palace place?
I'm talking about the Mermaid Princess!
S-She's there, but what about it?
Then I'll go. Even if it may kill me.
You're going?! Haven't you learned yet?!
If she's a beauty, you'll die instantly!
Ryuuguu Palace
"Hard-Shell Tower"
Hey! Are you done thinking yet?
Let's go outside!
I really... can't.
Why not?! You said there were places you wanted to go, right?
But if I do something so selfish,
I'll be causing trouble for everyone in the castle.
If I'd been locked up in here for ten years,
I'd have gone crazy.
This is to thank you for the food.
I'll be there with you, so where do you want to go?
Well...
To the Sea Forest!
N-No, but...
that's just a dream.
I couldn't possibly do something
as selfish as breaking out of here.
Why are you starting to cry just from saying where you want to go?!
I-I'm sorry.
I had to gather up so much courage just to say it.
P-Please don't be mad at me!
You're scary, Luffy-sama!
You're such a pain!
What?! What was that loud noise?!
Is he throwing something at us again?
What a rude guy.
What's that?
W-What is that sound -jamon?
Could it be Decken's doing?!
It's coming from Hard-Shell Tower -jamon!
S-S-Shirahoshi is in danger!
A-Are the guards with her?!
No, they're all tied up here!
H-Hey, pirates!
Go and ensure the princess' safety in place of the guards!
Huh? What're you talking about?
But Neptune-sama!
That means letting them know about the princess!
What choice do we have?!
Hard-Shell Tower is on the northeast side of the palace!
All of you, go there right now!
Why do we have to take orders from our hostage?
Silence! Shirahoshi is my only daughter!
For that reason, she's constantly being targeted!
If anything happens to my daughter, I will drive you into the bottom of the deep sea!
So basically, she is the Mermaid Princess? Am I right?
If so, I shall go to her as soon as I can!
And then...
I wonder if she will show me her panties?
Hey, wait, Brook!
Oh, what are we to do?!
He dashed off with indecent motives!
Now the princess is in danger
for an entirely different reason!
Wait, skeleton!
You can keep me tied up, but please take me with you!
Hard-Shell Tower is under my jurisdiction.
If anything happens to the princess,
I will never be at peace. Even in death!
You...
must...
really love her, right?
Don't be absurd!
How shameless!
No!
Sanji-san, I will be going there first if you don't mind!
I've always wanted to go to the Sea Forest.
All this time, throughout these past ten years.
But... everyone warns me that
it's too dangerous to leave the tower.
So I'm scared of going outside.
Luffy-sama, will you really take me there?
Sure.
Will you really protect me?
Leave it to me! It'll be fine!
Hey! If you're gonna cry, then I won't take you anywhere!
Besides, to be honest, it's more like you'll be taking me there.
I can't swim, after all.
I-I'm so sorry. I'm just too happy.
You really are a crybaby, huh?
And a weakling.
But if we go outside, you'll stand out so much that you'll get spotted right away.
Right... I'm so sorry.
So I have an idea to deal with that!
Mermaid Princess! Are you alright?
Hey, skeleton! Look at the side of the tower!
Huh?
That's insane! Those aren't the usual knives or axes that come flying!
That sound was human pirates crashing into the tower!
How bizarre!
That Vander Decken is insane!
What?! V-Vander Decken?!
This isn't good! They're getting up!
This means... Enemy soldiers have invaded the impenetrable Ryuuguu Palace!
This is a sneak attack! The king is in danger!
The princess is in danger!
The sounds of the attacks have stopped, right?
Let's go, weakling!
Y-Yes!
I'm counting on you, Megalo!
Go, shark!
Megalo!
Luffy-san!
To the Sea Forest!